hrw.com 2002-12-11

# Holt, Rinehart and Winston

  |  |   | 

**Holt, Rinehart and Winston Customer Privacy Policy**

THE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU COLLECTED ON THIS WEB SITE IS SUBJECT TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. BY DISCLOSING THE INFORMATION TO US, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THE POLICY. 

Holt, Rinehart and Winston recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of our customers and visitors to our Web site, while permitting us to conduct legitimate business by providing services and information of interest to our customers and visitors. Our privacy policy is stated below: 

**Collection and Storage of Information:**  
We will collect certain personal information including your name, address, and e-mail address when you register for our services, purchase our products, or request information. We maintain this information in our customer database. We may also collect additional information, such as in connection with special offers, contests, or other promotions. We may use "cookies" or other types of technology to recognize you and your access privileges on our site, as well as to track site usage. 

**Use of Information:**  
This information is used to provide the service or product requested; to enable billing and shipping; to provide you with information about related products and services, based on the preferences you have indicated; to improve our Web site; for development of new products and services; and for systems administration and troubleshooting purposes. 

**Your Rights:**  
Upon request, you may review and approve the information collected about you during registration in our customer database. Upon request, we will remove that information from our customer database or change/correct personal information that you state is erroneous. However, you should understand that information about you in our databases may come from a number of sources, including orders placed by you and third party mailing lists. 

**Privacy Contact:**  
Questions regarding this policy should be directed to Holt, Rinehart and Winston at [webmaster@hrw.com](mailto:webmaster@hrw.com). Holt, Rinehart and Winston is not responsible for the privacy policies of Web site to which this site may link. 

Due to the diverse nature of our businesses, companies within the Harcourt family may have privacy policies that differ from this policy. In such cases, the privacy policy of the particular Harcourt company will be posted and will supersede the terms of this document. 

|   |  |    
---  
  |
